inbenta.com 2019-12-24

# Privacy Policy - Inbenta

_Effective Date: November 13, 2019_

This privacy policy applies to our website ( [https://www.inbenta.com ](https://www.inbenta.com/)) and our service ( [https://backstage.inbenta.com ](https://backstage.inbenta.com/)) owned and operated by Inbenta Technologies Inc. (“We”, “Our”, “Us”) This privacy policy describes how Inbenta Technologies Inc. collects and uses the personal information you provide. It also describes the choices available to you regarding our use of your personal information and how you can access and update this information. The use of information collected through our service shall be limited to the purpose of providing the service for which the Client has engaged Inbenta Technologies Inc.

The services and products of INBENTA Technologies Inc are operated by:  
INBENTA HOLDINGS INC. SUCURSAL EN ESPAÑA  
CIF: W4008344F  
Address: Calle Aragó 222 Barcelona  
Contact email: privacy@inbenta.com  
All data related to personal information is processed at INBENTA HOLDINGS INC. SUCURSAL EN ESPAÑA and regulated by the European data protection regulation: European regulation 2016/679 on the protection of natural persons with regard to the processing of personal data and on the free movement of such data.

The EU-U.S. Privacy Shield Frameworks were designed by the U.S. Department of Commerce, and the European Commission and Swiss Administration, respectively, to provide companies on both sides of the Atlantic with a mechanism to comply with data protection requirements when transferring personal data from the European Union and Switzerland to the United States in support of transatlantic commerce.

Inbenta Technologies Inc. participates in and has certified its compliance with the EU-U.S. Privacy Shield Framework. We are committed to subjecting all personal data received from European Union (EU) member countries, the United Kingdom and Switzerland, in reliance on the Privacy Shield Framework, to the Framework’s applicable Principles. To learn more about the Privacy Shield Framework, visit the U.S. Department of Commerce’s Privacy Shield List, <https://www.privacyshield.gov/list>.

Inbenta Technologies Inc. is responsible for the processing of personal data it receives, under the Privacy Shield Framework, and subsequently transfers to a third party acting as an agent on its behalf. We comply with the Privacy Shield Principles for all onward transfers of personal data from the EU, including the onward transfer liability provisions.

With respect to personal data received or transferred pursuant to the Privacy Shield Framework, we are subject to the regulatory enforcement powers of the U.S. Federal Trade Commission. In certain situations, we may be required to disclose personal data in response to lawful requests by public authorities, including to meet national security or law enforcement requirements.

If you have an unresolved privacy or data use concern that we have not addressed satisfactorily, please contact our U.S.-based third-party dispute resolution provider (free of charge) at <https://feedback-form.truste.com/watchdog/request>.

Under certain conditions, more fully described on the Privacy Shield website, <https://www.privacyshield.gov/article?id=How-to-Submit-a-Complaint>, you may invoke binding arbitration when other dispute resolution procedures have been exhausted.

**Information Collection and Use**

We collect personal information from you such as your contact information, which may include but not limited to, your name, email address and phone number. We use this information to send you requested product or service information, contact you, respond to your customer service requests, administer your account and send you marketing communications.

**Information Related to Data Collected for our Clients**

Inbenta Technologies Inc. collects information under the direction of its Clients and has no direct relationship with the individuals whose personal data it processes. If you are a customer of one of our Clients and would no longer like to be contacted by one of our Clients that use our service, please contact the Client that you interact with directly. We may transfer personal information to companies that help us provide our service. Transfers to subsequent third parties are covered by the service agreements with our Clients.

**Information Sharing**

We may provide your personal information to companies that provide services to help us with our business activities such as shipping your order or offering customer service. These companies are authorized to use your personal information only as necessary to provide these services to us.

We may also disclose your personal information:

  * as required by law, such as to comply with a subpoena or similar legal process,
  * when we believe in good faith that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights, protect your safety or the safety of others, investigate fraud, or respond to a government request,
  * if Inbenta Technologies Inc. is involved in a merger, acquisition, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, you will be notified via email and/or a prominent notice on our Web site of any change in ownership or uses of your personal information, as well as any choices you may have regarding your personal information,
  * to any other third party with your prior consent to do so.

**User Access and Choice**

Upon request, we will provide you with information about whether we hold, or process on behalf of a third party, any of your personal information. If your personal information changes, or if you no longer desire our service, you may correct, update, amend, delete/remove or deactivate it [by contacting us either via email](https://www.inbenta.com/en/contact/), telephone or post at the contact information listed below. We will respond to your request to access within 30 days.

We will retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services. We will retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.

Receiving emails from our site is part of our service. You may receive service-related emails from us, which you do not have an option to opt out from. We may also send you marketing emails. Out of respect for your privacy, you may choose to stop receiving these marketing emails by following the unsubscribe instructions included in these emails.

**Access and Retention of Data Controlled by our Clients**

Inbenta Technologies Inc. acknowledges that you have the right to access your personal information. Inbenta Technologies Inc. has no direct relationship with the individuals whose personal data it processes. An individual who seeks access, or who seeks to correct, amend, or delete inaccurate data should direct his query to the Inbenta Technologies Inc.’s Client (the data controller). If requested to remove data we will respond within 30 days.

We will retain personal data we process on behalf of our Clients for as long as needed to provide services to our Client. Inbenta Technologies Inc. will retain this personal information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.

**Cookies and other Tracking Technologies**

Cookies and similar technologies are used by Inbenta Technologies Inc. and our partners, affiliates, or analytics or service providers. These technologies are used in analyzing trends, administering the site, tracking users’ movements around the site and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole. We may receive reports based on the use of these technologies by these companies on an individual as well as aggregated basis.

We use cookies for our online experience, to remember users’ settings (e.g. language preference), for authentication. Users can control the use of cookies at the individual browser level. If you reject cookies, you may still use our site, but your ability to use some features or areas of our site may be limited.

As is true of most websites, we gather certain information automatically and store it in log files. This information includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, and clickstream data.

We do not link this automatically collected data to other information we collect about you.

For more information, please consult the [_cookies policy_](https://www.inbenta.com/en/cookie-policy/).

**Advertising**

We partner with a third party to either display advertising on our Web site or to manage our advertising on other sites. Our third party partner may use cookies or similar technologies to gather information about your activities on this site and other sites in order to provide you advertising based upon your browsing activities and interests. If you wish to not have this information used for the purpose of serving you interest-based ads, you may opt-out by clicking [here](https://preferences-mgr.truste.com/) (or if located in the European Union click [here](http://www.youronlinechoices.eu/)). Please note this does not opt you out of being served ads. You will continue to receive generic ads.

**Security**

The security of your personal information is important to us. When you enter sensitive information (such as login credentials) on our order forms, we encrypt the transmission of that information using secure socket layer technology (SSL).

We follow generally accepted standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. If you have any questions about security on our Website, please contact us at _[privacy@inbenta.com](mailto:privacy@inbenta.com)_.

**Links to 3rd party sites**

Our Site includes links to other Web sites whose privacy practices may differ from those of Inbenta Technologies Inc. If you submit personal information to any of those sites, your information is governed by their privacy policies. We encourage you to carefully read the privacy policy of any Web site you visit.

**Testimonials**

We display personal testimonials of satisfied customers on our site in addition to other endorsements. With your consent, we may post your testimonial along with your name. If you wish to update or delete your testimonial, please [contact us](https://www.inbenta.com/en/contact/).

**Social Media Widgets**

Our Web site includes Social Media Features, such as the Facebook and Twitter buttons and Widgets, such as the Share this button or interactive mini-programs that run on our site. These Features may collect your IP address, which page you are visiting on our site, and may set a cookie to enable the Feature to function properly. Social Media Features and Widgets are either hosted by a third party or hosted directly on our Site. Your interactions with these Features are governed by the privacy policy of the company providing it.

**Changes to this Privacy Policy**

We may update this privacy policy to reflect changes to our information practices. If we make any material changes we will notify you by email (sent to the e-mail address specified in your account) or by means of a notice on this Site prior to the change becoming effective. We encourage you to periodically review this page for the latest information on our privacy practices.

**Contact Us**

Inbenta Holdings Inc.  
1065 E. Hillsdale Blvd. Suite 425  
Foster City, CA, 94404  
Tel. +1 (408) 213-8771  
Email:  _[privacy@inbenta.com](mailto:privacy@inbenta.com)_

_[Legal notice](https://www.inbenta.com/en/about-us/legal-notice-and-disclaimer)_  
_[General Terms of Service](https://www.inbenta.com/en/tos/)_  
_[Inbenta Service Level Agreement](https://www.inbenta.com/en/sla/)_
